<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_all.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?>
<?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_all.rng" type="application/xml"
	schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>Title</title>
         </titleStmt>
         <This transcription follows a diplomatic approach, reproducing the text as it appears in the original document as closely as possible. Original spelling, capitalization, punctuation, and formatting have been preserved in order to maintain the historical and material integrity of the source text.
Line breaks, paragraph divisions, and spacing have been retained where they are visually evident in the document. Structural features such as headings, section titles, and date markers have also been preserved, as they contribute to the organization and rhetorical presentation of the text. Emphatic capitalization in headings (such as section titles describing events or themes) has been maintained.
No modernization or correction of spelling and grammar has been undertaken. Apparent typographical irregularities such as “ammner,” “grraft,” “intende,” “constribution” and hyphenated or broken words such as “in-vestigator” or “cri-minal” have been preserved as they appear in the source. These features are treated as part of the original document rather than errors to be corrected.
Editorial intervention has been kept to a minimum. Where necessary, unclear or ambiguous text has been transcribed conservatively without interpretation. This approach ensures consistency across the transcription and preserves the textual features required for accurate TEI encoding, while allowing for the possibility of later normalization or correction using TEI markup. 
>
            <p>Publication Information</p>
         </publicationStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <p>Information about the source</p>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
  </teiHeader>
  <text>
      <body>
         <p>Some text here. additional text</p>
      </body>
  </text>
</TEI>
